# MARINA COBB

# GRAPHIC DESIGNER, MARKETER, AND CONTINUOUS LEARNER. -

COBBMARIN@GMAIL.COM

317.914.2790

INDIANAPOLIS, INDIANA

WWW MARINACOBB COM

I am 7 years into my craft of visual communications with a curious and playful nature. I light up at the idea of a challenge where I can use my creative skills to solve a problem. I truly believe that hard work, dedication and practice is the formula that will take my skills to the top. Everyday I am looking to practice design thinking; everyday I am dedicated to my craft and enhancing my graphic and technical skills. I am looking for a career that will not only push my creativity, but also one that is flexible enough to help foster me as I grow.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2016 - Present Old Town Design Group MARKETING COORDINATOR

- Creative lead with focus on community branding
- Lead videographer and digital marketer (websites, e-mails & social media)
- Implement & track marketing campaigns
- Prepare Google analytic reports
- · Create & maintain marketing materials
- In charge of apparels from creation to distribution
- Head of marketing home listings and Realtor showings

2014 - 2016 PERQ

PRINT PRODUCTION ARTIST

- Proofed and preflight newspaper ads
- Created artwork for lead generation of auto sales
- Developed templates to use for seasonal purposes
- Efficiently and accurately take a design from conception into a print-ready piece
- Create E-blasts, gifs, buttons, web banners and micro-sites for events

2012 - 2014 Gannett / Indy Star GRAPHIC ARTIST

- Designing advertisements in newspapers, magazines, and other publications
- Learned to efficiently use Adobe programs
- · Meet press deadlines while maintaining accuracy
- Successfully complete accuracy, quality, and quota prerequisites

# **EDUCATION**

2009 - 2012 Herron School of Art & Design BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS - VISUAL COMMUNICATIONS

#### **VOLUNTEER**

MISTY EYES ANIMAL CENTER
Creation of marketing materials for donations.

#### SAFE FAMILIES

Helped to remodel a home that will provide residence to local families in crisis.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

INDESIGN
PHOTOSHOP
ILLUSTRATOR
PREMIERE PRO
MAIL CHIMP
SQUARESPACE
WORDPRESS
MICROSOFT OFFICE
SALESFORCE

# PERSONAL SKILLS

- Page Layouts
- Pre-press knowledge
- Typography
- Color Theory
- Sketching
- Branding
- Marketing
- Concept Development
- Critical/Analytical Thinking

- Web Design
- Wire framing
- Customer Service
- Written/Verbal/Visual Communication
- Information Technology
- Project Management
- Leadership and Personal Development

# **VISIT MY PORTFOLIO SITE AT:**

MARINACOBB.COM | REACH ME AT: 317.914.2790